Guide to "Suits Me: The Double Life of Billy Tipton" Research and Production Records SC0608
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiovisual material, Series 5
  - Kitty Oakes Interviews
    - 1992 January 12 (Tape 4), 1992-01-12; 26; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 January 12 (Tape 5), 1992-01-12; 27; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 January 12 (Tape 6), 1992-01-12; 28; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 January 12 (Tape 7), 1992-01-12; 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 January 13 (Tape 8), 1992-01-13; 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 March 19 (Tape 9), 1992-03-19; 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 March 19 (Tape 10), 1992-03-19; 32; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 March 20 (Tape 11), 1992-03-20; 33; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - 1992 March 23 (Tape 12), 1992-03-23; 34; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Spokane, WA 1995 January 24, 1995-01-24; 35; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Kitty on marriage and divorce, 1995 May 3; phone call from London on divorce, 1996 July 20, 1995-1996; 25; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Sex questions, 1995 November 18, 2008, 1995-2008; 26; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Fact checking (1), 1996 July 14, 1996-07-14; 27; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Fact checking (2), 1996 July 15, 1996-07-15; 28; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Kitty on [lying?], 1996 July 28, 1996-07-28; 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Kitty on divorce, 1996 July 20, 1996-07-20; 30; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
  - Interviews
    - Ball, Don, Spokane, WA, 1995 January 28, 1995-01-28; 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Ball, Don, 1996 July 25, 1996-07-25; 32; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Bamonte, Tony, 1995 May 5, 1995-05-05; 33; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Benson, Wayne, 1994 August 2, 1994-08-02; 34; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Blair, Birney, Spokane WA, 1995 May 4, 1995-05-04; 35; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Brandon, Joanne, 1996 September 25, 1996-09-25; 36; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Brandon, Mike, fact-checking phone call from London, 1996 July 25; NPR on women in jazz, 1996-07-25; 37; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Brandon, Mike, Spokane WA, 1995 January 31, 1995-01-31; 38; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Brower, Roberta, 1995 June 10 [1 of 2] [transcribed 1995 July 25-26], 1995-06-10; 39; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Brower, Roberta, 1995 June 10-11 [2 of 2], 1995-06-10; 40; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Brown, [Jeri?], Spokane WA, 1995 November 16, 1995-11-16; 41; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cagle, Clarence and Katherine, Tulsa OK, 1994 January 28 [1 of 2], 1994-01-28; 42; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cagle, Clarence and Katherine, Tulsa OK, 1994 January 28 [2 of 2], 1994-01-28; 43; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Carlyle, Russ, 1996 February 13, 1996-02-13; 44; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cattanach, Maryann, 1993 April 23 [2 of 2] [transcribed 1995 February], 1993-04-23; 45; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cattanach, Maryann, 1993 April 24, 1993-04-24; 46; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cox, Betty, 1993 March 6 [1 of 2] [transcribed 1993 August], 1993-03-06; 47; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cox, Betty, 1993 March 6 [2 of 2] [transcribed 1995 August 5], 1993-03-06; 48; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cox, Betty, 1994 February 2 [side one only; side 2 blank], 1994-02-02; 49; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cox, Betty, drive to Joplin, 1994 February 2 [1 of 2] [transcribed 1995 August], 1994-02-02; 50; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cox, Betty, drive to Joplin, 1994 February 2 [2 of 2] [transcribed 1995 August], 1994-02-02; 51; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cunningham, Patty on Terry Whitt, 1995 May 31, 1995-05-31; 52; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - “Don comments on sites in Moore OK and Oklahoma City, 4/95”, 1994-04; 53; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - “Driving to KC [illegible]”, 1995 April 23” [attached via rubber band to tape above], 1995-04-23; 54; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Eagle, Don, 1995 May 3, 1995-05-03; 55; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Grandemain, K., 1997 March 29, 1997-03-29; 56; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Green, Jamison, Emeryville, 1993 February 18, 1993-02-18; 57; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Handler, Shannon, 1900-01-00; 58; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Harmion, Clint, 1996 November 16, 1996-11-16; 59; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Hill, Marigold, 1997 April 24 (1 of 2), 1997-04-24; 60; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Hornell(?), Lela, Oklahoma City home of Sara Murphy, 1994 July 31, 1994-07-31; 61; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Jensen, Paul, 1994 February 11 [transcribed 1994 February 11], 1994-02-11; 62; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Jensen, Paul, 1995 April 22 [transcribed 1995 July 11-12], 1995-04-22; 63; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Jensen, Paul, 1995 August 5, 1996 January 17, 1995-08-05; 64; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Jones, Christine, 1997 September, 1997-09; 65; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Kilde, Ron, 1995 April 28 [1 of 3], 1995-04-28; 66; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Kilde, Ron, 1995 April 28 [2 of 3], 1995-04-28; 67; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Kilde, Ron, 1995 April 29 [3 of 3] [partially transcribed], 1995-04-29; 68; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Lane, Pauline, Oklahoma City, OK, 1995 March 30, 1995-03-30; 69; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Lent, Shirley, 1993 January 25, 1993-01-25; 70; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Mallet, Jack, 1996 January 24; Haddix, C., 1996 March 6, 1905-06-18; 71; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Murphy, Sara, by phone, 1994 February 25, 1994-02-25; 72; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Murphy, Sara, on the Arkansawyers, Oklahoma City, OK, 1994 July 31, 1994-07-31; 73; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Murphy, Sara/Lillian, 1997 January 22, 1997-01-22; 74; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Neighbors and Teachers, Spokane WA, 1995 November 19, 1995-11-19; 75; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Numbers, Jerry, 1995 November 17, 1995-11-17; 76; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Oakes, Bob, 1995 January 29, 1995-01-29; 77; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - O’Neil, 1997 May 30, 1997-05-30; 78; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - O’Neil, Dick, Spokane WA, 1995 January 30, 1995-01-30; 79; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Pearce, Euline, 1992 October 4 [transcribed 1995 August], 1992-10-04; 80; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Perkins, Tommy, Oklahoma City OK, 1994 January 23, 1994-01-23; 81; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Phone checking info, Kilde and O’Neil, 1996 March, 1996-03; 83; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Pierson, Bill, Joplin MO, 1995 April 22 [transcribed 1995 July 8-9], 1995-04-22; 84; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Raines, Lew, 1995 April 21 [1 of 2] [transcribed], 1995-04-21; 85; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Raines, Lew, 1995 April 21 [1 of 2] [transcribed 1995 July 6-7], 1995-04-21; 86; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Review of autopsy report, 1993 August, 1993-08; 87; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Richards, Kenny and Dolly, 1995 November 14 [1 of 2], 1995-11-14; 88; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Richards, Kenny and Dolly, 1995 November 14 [2 of 2], 1995-11-14; 89; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Richter, Marvin, 1995 November 22, 1995-11-22; 90; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Ronconi, Elaine, 1996 January 5 and 22, 1996-01; 91; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Rotchford, Bob, Spokane WA, 1995 May 4, 1995-05-04; 92; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Seaton, Jerry, 1995 April 22 [transcribed 1995 July 12], 1995-04-22; 93; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - “She Even Chewed Tobacco (sound)”, 1900-01-00; 94; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Sobol, Dave, Scottsdale, 1995 January 31 [1 of 2], 1995-01-31; 95; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Sobol, Dave, Scottsdale, 1995 January 31 [2 of 2], 1995-01-31; 96; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Sobol, Dave, 1995 May 2, 1995-05-02; 97; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Spencer, Bonnie, Oklahoma City, OK, 1995 March 29, 1995-03-29; 98; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Spencer, Bonnie, Lincoln County Historical Society, 1995 March 30, 1995-03-30; 99; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Stringfellow, Barron, 1997 April 4, 1997-04-04; 100; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Swan, K. (Betty), 1994 February 15, 1994-02-15; 101; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Swan, Madeline, 1992 October 1 [transcribed 1993] August [1 of 2], 1992-10-01; 102; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Swan, Madeline, 1992 October 1 [transcribed 1993] August [2 of 2], 1992-10-01; 103; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Teagarden, Norma, 1993 February 11 [transcribed], 1993-02-11; 104; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T., 1996 February 10-11, 1996-02-11; 105; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T. on Kansas City, 1996 November 16, 1996-11-16; 106; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T. on Kansas City, 1997 January, 1997-01; 107; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T., Sun City, 1996 February 12 [transcribed 1996 March 15] [tape 2], 1996-02-12; 108; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T., 1994 July 25, 1994-07-25; 109; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T. and Doris, 1993 January 31 [tape 4], 1993-01-31; 110; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T., 1993 January 30 [tape 1], 1993-01-30; 111; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T., Sun City, 1993 January 29 [2 of 2], 1993-01-29; 112; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Tipton, William T., Sun City, 1993 January 29 [1 of 2], 1993-01-29; 113; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Watson, Bill, 1995 November 20, 1995-11-20; 114; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Wallin, “Son,” 1994 January 25 [transcribed 1994 May 1], 1994-01-25; 115; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Wallin fact checking, 1997 February 16 / Follow-up letter of Feb. 17, 1997 February 28, 1997-02-16; 116; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Benson, Wayne, 1997 March 8, 1997-03-08; 117; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Boeckman, C., re: Mayer, 1997 March 12, 1997-03-12; 118; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cagle, fact checking, 1997 February 8 / Bob Lee messages, 1997 February 12, 1997-02-08; 119; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Cox, Betty, 1997 March 31, 1997-03-31; 120; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Delaverie, Stormie, 1996 December 12, 1996-12-12; 121; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Grandemain, K. re: George Mayer, 1997 March 16, 1997-03-16; 122; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Raines, Lewis, 1997 February 17, 1997-02-17; 123; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Rice, Lucille, 1997 March 1, 1997-03-01; 124; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Roseburg OR[?] historian, 1997 April 10, 1997-04-10; 125; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
    - Short interviews with Bob Lee Informants: LaPlante, Craddock, Rhoden, 1997 February 14, 1997-02-14; 126; 1 audiocassette(s) (microcassette) (Box 16)
- Billy Tipton book files, Accession ARCH-2001-014
  - Folders: Afterfile of Billy T through Ronconi [transcripts of interviews, copies of documents, correspondence, chron files] (Box 1A)
  - Middlebrooks' logbooks, 1992-Feb. 1995 and February 1995-January 1996 (Box 1B)
  - Folder: 1961-68 Tipton: letters (copies of) (Box 1B)
  - Advance reading copy of Suits Me (Box 1B)
  - Assorted folders on Oklahoma (Box 1B)
  - Folder: Screenplay by Kate Wright "The Billy Tipton Story" (Box 1B)
  - Topic files on gender (Box 1B)
  - Chronological files in notebook [research on Tipton arranged chronologically] (Box 1B)
  - NY Times with Tipton's obituary (Box 1B)
  - Photocopies of illustrations (Box 2A)
  - Inventory of Billy Tipton's scrapbooks and office records prepared by Mary Ellen Foley (Box 2A)
  - Assorted books on Oklahoma history (Box 2A)
  - Metal case ("Grandma's Favorites") owned by Carrie Flaherty [Kitty Tipton's mother] containing family photographs (Box 2A)
  - Folders: S through Wilson, Teddy [transcripts of interviews, copies of documents, correspondence, chron files] (Box 2B)
  - Chapter revisions [2 notebooks] (Box 2B)
  - Typescript of book (Box 2B)
  - Logbook (Box 2B)
  - Folders: BT chron files, place files, business file, FTM newsletter 1987-97, miscellaneous research files (Box 3)
  - Jerry Everding's notes on Joplin, Missouri (Box 4)
  - Name index leads (Box 4)
  - Reviews, clippings, magazines, notes, and correspondence; interview audiotapes; audiotape copies of Tipton's music (Box 5)
  - Photographs and inventory of photographs (Box 6)
  - Primary B.T.: primary documents [autopsy, death certificate, deeds, etc.] (Box 7)
  - Hardback copy of final book Suits Me, The Double Life of Billy Tipton (Box 7)
  - Assorted books for background research (Box 7)
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH-2015-094
  - Self-Made Man: A Life of Billy Tipton [draft], 1996 Oct 2 (Box 1)